https://phohoa.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We want to make your experience with our "site" (www.phohoa.com) as enjoyable as possible. We also believe you have the right to browse our site anonymously. For this reason, we provide you with the means to control your privacy and welcome you to submit any questions or concerns that you may have. Please read this information carefully before accessing any part of this site.
Information is collected from you to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. We use this information to craft initiatives that are designed as a platform to deliver a broad range of personalized products and services to our customers across our consumer brands. By knowing customer preferences, services and special offerings can be tailored to eliminate hassles and provide superior levels of convenience on a one-to-one basis. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, e-mail address or information concerning what you like and do not like. On other occasions when we provide items for purchase online, we may request your credit card number to conclude the transaction or your mailing address to insure proper delivery. In each case, we are committed to protecting your information and will never use your information in a manner that you do not authorize.
We want you and your family to be safe while visiting our Internet sites. That is why, consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from children.
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information in several different ways. We indirectly collect through third party providers the domain name of visitors to our Web pages, IP addresses, information concerning your browsing interests on the Site, and we may directly collect any information that you voluntarily submit such as name, e-mail addresses, survey results, postal address, telephone numbers and other information that you provide voluntarily. Like many other commercial web sites, our web sites may employ a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect and store information while browsing our Site, which may be used by third party providers. You may set your browser to refuse the “cookie”, but there may be pages on our Site you will not be able to access if you do. Our Site, however, does not recognize individual users. We also welcome submission of your comments, suggestions and criticisms and will use this information to improve our products and services. If you wish to be excluded, you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” of the marketing use of your information at the time that we contact you.
Who is Collecting the Information?
Ownership of any information you provide us may be held by Pho Hoa Noodle Soup and our third party providers alone. We will not sell ownership of this data to any other company or organization.
How Is The Information Used?
We use the information that we may collect to understand your preferences and history. With this information we can tailor our services and special offerings to provide superior levels of information and convenience. We also use the collected information to improve the design of the pages on the Site. If you provide us with your e-mail address, we may occasionally send you email offers, informing you about products and services. If you provide us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. These offers may be based on information you provided us in your responses to our surveys and on your history with us as a customer. Any other use of your information will be explained in advance and will be subject to your express consent, which consent shall be granted upon entry and submission of that information.
Information Distribution
If you are providing personal information, it will only be used within our domain unless you expressly consent to allow third party data sharing. Although unlikely, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to the appropriate governmental authorities. If requested as part of a legal proceeding, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation.
There may be links that will let you leave the Site. We do not control the links or their sites and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement of the site. The use and/or privacy provided by the operator of a linked site as to any information you provide in accessing a linked site is in no way subject to our privacy policy. Each linked site may have its own policy that could differ considerably from our policy, or the linked site may not display any privacy policy at all.
Security Procedures
We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. Any particularly sensitive information, such as a customer's credit card number, is encrypted prior to transmission. Access to your information is limited to the small set of employees that manage the Site and our network.
How You Can Correct Any Inaccuracies in the Information
You have the ability to edit the personal information that you have provided to us. To update the information retained about you, please “unsubscribe,” and then “subscribe” to re-submit your information.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this Site, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We may also change the policy from time to time, so please be sure to visit this Site often to see if anything has changed. If we post changes and you continue to use the Site, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about the Policy of this Site, please email us at marketing (at) phohoa (dot) com.
